<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>uRemoTech</title>
    <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uRemotech.de/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>uRemoTech</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-gb</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://uRemotech.de/media/logo_huf6c28dd88df8877b5dcc9b76d0760344_62324_300x300_fit_lanczos_3.png</url>
      <title>uRemoTech</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uRemotech.de/en/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-according-to-section-5-tmg&#34;&gt;Data according to Section 5 TMG&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;uRemoTech GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG &lt;br&gt;
Kieler Str. 20a, &lt;br&gt;
24582 Bordesholm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Represented by:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Lennart Röder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact details&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
E-Mail: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Lennart.Roeder@uRemoTech.de&#34;&gt;Lennart.Roeder@uRemoTech.de&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Registration number: HRA 11546 KI &lt;br&gt;
Court: Kiel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tax ID&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
DE352558049&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uRemotech.de/en/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The person responsible within the meaning of the data protection laws, in particular the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;uRemoTech GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-data-subject-rights&#34;&gt;Your data subject rights&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can exercise the following rights at any time using the contact details provided for our data protection officer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information about your data stored by us and their processing (Article 15 GDPR),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Correction of incorrect personal data (Article 16 GDPR),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deletion of your data stored by us (Article 17 GDPR),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restriction of data processing if we are not yet allowed to delete your data due to legal obligations (Article 18 GDPR),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objection to the processing of your data by us (Article 21 GDPR) and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data transferability if you have consented to data processing or have concluded a contract with us (Article 20 GDPR).
If you have given us your consent, you can revoke this at any time with effect for the future.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can contact a supervisory authority at any time with a complaint, e.g. B. to the competent supervisory authority of the federal state of your place of residence or to the authority responsible for us as the responsible body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A list of the supervisory authorities (for the non-public area) with addresses can be found at: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Service/Anschriften/Laender/Laender-node.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Service/Anschriften/Laender/Laender-node.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-form&#34;&gt;contact form&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;type-and-purpose-of-processing&#34;&gt;Type and purpose of processing&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The data you enter will be stored for the purpose of individual communication with you. This requires you to provide a valid email address and your name. This is used to allocate the request and then to answer it. Providing further data is optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;legal-basis&#34;&gt;Legal basis&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The data entered in the contact form is processed on the basis of a legitimate interest (Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By providing the contact form, we would like to make it easy for you to contact us. The information you provide will be stored for the purpose of processing the request and for possible follow-up questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you contact us to request an offer, the data entered in the contact form will be processed to carry out pre-contractual measures (Article 6 (1) (b) GDPR).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;recipient&#34;&gt;Recipient&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recipients of the data may be processors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;storage-duration&#34;&gt;Storage duration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data will be deleted no later than 6 months after processing the request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there is a contractual relationship, we are subject to the statutory retention periods according to the German Commercial Code and delete your data after these periods have expired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;provision-prescribed-or-required&#34;&gt;Provision prescribed or required&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The provision of your personal data is voluntary. However, we can only process your request if you provide us with your name, email address and the reason for the request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-of-script-libraries-google-webfonts&#34;&gt;Use of script libraries (Google Webfonts)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to display our content correctly and graphically appealing across browsers, we use &amp;ldquo;Google Web Fonts&amp;rdquo; from Google LLC (1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA; hereinafter &amp;ldquo;Google&amp;rdquo;) to display fonts on this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find more information about Google Web Fonts at &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq&lt;/a&gt; and in Google&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ssl-encryption&#34;&gt;SSL encryption&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to protect the security of your data during transmission, we use state-of-the-art encryption methods (e.g. SSL) via HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-about-your-right-of-objection-according-to-art-21-gdpr&#34;&gt;Information about your right of objection according to Art. 21 GDPR&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;individual-right-of-objection&#34;&gt;Individual right of objection&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have the right, for reasons arising from your particular situation, to object at any time to the processing of personal data relating to you, which is based on Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR (data processing on the basis of a balance of interests); this also applies to profiling based on this provision within the meaning of Art. 4 No. 4 GDPR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you file an objection, we will no longer process your personal data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for processing that outweigh your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing serves to assert, exercise or defend legal claims.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;recipient-of-an-objection&#34;&gt;Recipient of an objection&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;change-to-our-privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Change to our privacy policy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right to adapt this data protection declaration so that it always corresponds to the current legal requirements or to implement changes to our services in the data protection declaration, e.g. when introducing new services. The new data protection declaration will then apply to your next visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;questions-to-the-data-protection-officer&#34;&gt;Questions to the data protection officer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about data protection, please send us an email or contact the person responsible for data protection in our organization directly: Lennart Röder&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
