<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts | uRemoTech – IT-Beratung</title>
    <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uRemotech.de/en/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Abouts</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://uRemotech.de/media/logo_hu15029807518345716135.png</url>
      <title>Abouts</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission &amp; Vision</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/vision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;mission&#34;&gt;Mission&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Win-Win - Your success is our success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to lead your project to success with the help of our best experts at the highest level. We are here to stimulate your growth, identify and unleash untapped potential and enable you to react faster to changing market developments.
Our passion for technological excellence drives our success. Many small, medium and large &lt;a href=&#34;https://uRemotech.de/en/#references&#34;&gt;companies&lt;/a&gt; already value our commitment and expertise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to help you navigate the technological landscape and pave the way for your sustainable success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;vision&#34;&gt;Vision&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What once started small is set to become really big in the next 10 years! We want to set a new benchmark in the market and give all companies out there the opportunity to use their full digital potential in a customized way. We work every day to become the most modern, innovative and fastest-growing IT consultancy, unrivaled in progress and technological excellence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our History</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/history/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I myself was employed as an IT consultant. I implemented projects for customers and advised them. I kept asking myself the question: Why do we always do it the same way? There&amp;rsquo;s a much more efficient way! I had a vision and a goal: my aim is to reinterpret the world of IT consulting in order to change the status quo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to make processes more efficient, be freer in the execution of my work, give customers an even better experience and work with people who pursue the same goals as I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is exactly why I founded uRemoTech. A place where customers not only receive the best advice, but also find individual, practical solutions for their specific challenges. At the same time, uRemoTech offers employees the opportunity to take on responsibility, to continuously develop themselves and to harmoniously combine their professional and private lives. No more hour-long commutes, instead efficient working from home - supported by the latest technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, the name uRemoTech proudly stands for the 3 fundamental pillars of the company:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; srcset=&#34;
               /media/pages/our_story_hu3996292760586740670.webp 400w,
               /media/pages/our_story_hu2560068040719710360.webp 760w,
               /media/pages/our_story_hu11842833182360276360.webp 1200w&#34;
               src=&#34;https://uRemotech.de/media/pages/our_story_hu3996292760586740670.webp&#34;
               width=&#34;721&#34;
               height=&#34;657&#34;
               loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;u-you-stands-for-you&#34;&gt;u (you) stands for you:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are the center of attention! As an employee or customer for our service-oriented approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;remo-remote&#34;&gt;Remo (Remote):&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symbolizes our 100% remote approach that we not only live, but also promote. This approach enables our team members to realize a flexible combination of private life and work in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age and thus creates an innovative way of working together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;tech-technology&#34;&gt;Tech (technology):&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tech symbolizes innovation. It is progress not only for us, but for everything in life and we are a part of it. Our focus is on the adept use of state-of-the-art technology to achieve technological excellence. Always with the aim of taking our customers to the next evolutionary stage of digitalization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the founding of uRemoTech, the I became a we. &lt;br&gt;
I am proud of my growing team that shares these values! Today, we are joined by more and more like-minded people who believe in our vision, live it every day and drive it forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lennart Röder, CEO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Team</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;team-container&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://uRemotech.de/team/Lennart_circle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Lennart Foto&#34; class=&#34;avatar-circle&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;details&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Lennart&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;job-title&#34;&gt;Geschäftsführer /&lt;br&gt; IT-Berater (DevOps)&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Lennart has over 15 years of experience in the IT-industry and specialises in DevOps automation.&lt;br&gt; He manages the company and keeps an eye on the big picture.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://uRemotech.de/team/Azzurra_circle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Azzurra Foto&#34; class=&#34;avatar-circle&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;details&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Azzurra&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;job-title&#34;&gt;Assistenz der Geschäftsführung / Recruiterin&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Azzurra supports Lennart and is in charge of recruiting.&lt;br&gt;
      She always finds the best talent for our team and is characterised by her ability to improve team dynamics and create a positive working environment.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;break&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://uRemotech.de/team/Jan_circle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jan Foto&#34; class=&#34;avatar-circle&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;details&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Jan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;job-title&#34;&gt;IT-Berater (Fullstack)&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Jan is an experienced full-stack developer specialising in modern web technologies.&lt;br&gt;
      This includes Java/Kotlin, React.js, but also Kubernetes and AWS.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://uRemotech.de/team/Tobias_circle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tobias Foto&#34; class=&#34;avatar-circle&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;details&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Tobias&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;job-title&#34;&gt;IT-Berater (DevOps)&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Tobias is an experienced DevOps engineer who specialises in automation and infrastructure management.&lt;br&gt;
      Technologies like Kubernetes, GitOps and Helm are his daily bread.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- &lt;div class=&#34;break&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;
  &lt;!-- &lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://uRemotech.de/team/Tim_circle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tim Foto&#34; class=&#34;avatar-circle&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;details&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Tim&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;job-title&#34;&gt;ext. IT-Berater (Backend)&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Tim is an external consultant for backend development.&lt;br&gt;
      With his in-depth expertise in Java, Kotlin and Quarkus, he actively supports us.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Values</title>
      <link>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uRemotech.de/en/about/values/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-passion&#34;&gt;1. Passion&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Motivation gives us the impetus to take the first step. Consistency is the key to achieving our goals. We are dedicated and passionate about both our customers and our own team. We are prepared to go the extra mile to promote growth - not only for our customers, but also in our own company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;2-achieving-more-together&#34;&gt;2. Achieving more together&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strong individuals make up our team. We believe that the synergies created through teamwork allow us to not only hit the target, but to go far beyond it.
At our company, we know that teamwork is crucial to our success. Each team member contributes unique talents and skills that strengthen our community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;3-continuous-growth&#34;&gt;3. Continuous growth&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For us, continuous personal and professional development is the lifeblood of the current and future success of the individual, the team and therefore the entire company. We promote the continuous and ongoing development of all our employees through tailored offers and individual career planning. We believe that the growth of uRemoTech is directly proportional to the growth of each of our employees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;4-freedom-and-flexibility&#34;&gt;4. Freedom and flexibility&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Combining work with friends and family is the most important aspect of a modern world. We work a lot, we like to work. But besides work, there are many other things that are important in life. That&amp;rsquo;s why we have created a 100% remote working approach and flexible working hours so that you can combine work and private life. This is exactly how we create a completely different way of working and have the best team, regardless of the location of the individual employee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;5-personal-responsibility--cooperative-leadership&#34;&gt;5. personal responsibility &amp;amp; cooperative leadership&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want all our employees to actively participate in the development of the company by making their contribution conscientiously and responsibly. Our collaborative leadership style encourages individuals to make responsible strategic decisions for the benefit and progress of uRemoTech.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
